module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What date is "Devil\'s Night" celebrated?', 
    a: 'Oct 30',
    b: 'Oct 31',
    c: 'Nov 1',
    d: 'Dec 24',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'The first jack-o-lanterns were carved out of what vegetable?', 
    a: 'Pumpkins',
    b: 'Turnips',
    c: 'Melons',
    d: 'Squash',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is the main antagonist of the movie Ghostbusters?', 
    a: 'Ghostface Killer',
    b: 'Gozer',
    c: 'Slimer',
    d: 'The Nightmare Before Christmas',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What 1984 song features spoken words performed by Vincent Price?', 
    a: 'Werewolves of London',
    b: 'Monster Mash',
    c: 'This Is Halloween',
    d: 'Thriller',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Instead of Halloween, which country celebrates "The Day of the Dead"?', 
    a: 'Transylvania',
    b: 'Spain',
    c: 'Canada',
    d: 'Mexico',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Historically, during a bobbing for apples game, the first person to bite an apple would be next to ____', 
    a: 'Get Married',
    b: 'Be Sacrified',
    c: 'Get Rich',
    d: 'Have Children',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the first name of Dr. Frankenstein?', 
    a: 'Johann',
    b: 'Victor',
    c: 'Henry',
    d: 'Vincent',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who portrayed the iconic SNL character David S. Pumpkins', 
    a: 'Bobby Moynihan',
    b: 'Tim Allen',
    c: 'Jimmy Fallon',
    d: 'Tom Hanks',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was the Michael Meyers mask originally a mask of?', 
    a: 'Richard Nixon',
    b: 'Leonard Nimoy',
    c: 'William Shatner',
    d: 'JFK',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Jack Skellington\'s dog\'s name?', 
    a: 'Oogie Boogie',
    b: 'Zero',
    c: 'Barrel',
    d: 'Bones',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];